Guide to the Records of the Program in Archival Management 1978-1994 RG.20.3
New York University Archives
- Series I: Materials
  - Needs to be Filed…Students, undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Thellen, David: "Memory & American History", undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Thibodeau, Sharon Gibbs: "Archival Arrangement & Description", undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Sussman, Warren: "History & The American Intellectual: The Uses of a Usable Past", undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Swanson, Dorothy: "Tamiment Wagner Labor Archives", undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Storm-Clark, Christopher: "The Miners': 1870-1970: A Test", undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Steward, Virginia: "Problems of Confidentiality in the Administration of Personal Case Records", undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Stewart, V. & Ritzenthaler, M.: "Constituencies of Urban Archives: Donors, Users, and Institutions", undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Spring, Joel: "Mass Culture & School Sports", undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227167 9
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Student Records, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - G57.2012, Oral History, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227168 7
  - Advanced Internship in Archival Management, G57.2011, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Museum Studies, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Syllabi of Other Schools' Courses in Archives, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Inquiries, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Applicants, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Applicants, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Students, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Students, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - AMC Description, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - AMC Systems, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - AMC Authority Control, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - AMC RLIN, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Conservation, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Conservation, undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Acquisition (Constituencies), undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Automation, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Access, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - National Archives, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Historiography, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Historical Editing Readings, undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Government Records, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Ethics & Legalities, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Guest Speakers: Faculty and Others, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Articles & Pamphlets on Archives Program Misc., undated (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Funding: Grants & Fellowships, undated (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Weinstein & Booth: Uses for Historical Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Weber, Lisa: "Educating Archivists for Automation", undated (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Photographs: Samples of Conservation Problems, undated (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Williams, Harry: "Oral History & The Writing of", undated (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Walters, Tyler: "Possible Educations for Archivists: Integrating Grad. Archival Education with Public History Education Programs", 1991 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Vansina, Jan: "Once Upon A Time: Oral Traditions As History In Africa", undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Turner, Robert S.: "To Repair or Dispair?", undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - G57.2010 Spring, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 06327950 2
  - 1010 Find exam, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - G57.2017 Frusciano, Fall, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Research Essay, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    bar code #:3 1142 06327950 2
  - G57.1010 Fall, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227170 3
  - 2010 Orig., undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Orig. Fall-Spring, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1010 Master, Fall, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Curriculum, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Town Hall, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Practicum, Spring, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Intro. Course Syllabi, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Class Materials and Lecture Notes, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Search, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Co-Director, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - G57.2010, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Spring, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 2010 Syllabus, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Newsletter, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Owen Visit, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Grid Players, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - GSAS Director of Archives, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Historical Editing, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Photo Project: Practicum, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 1010 Lecture Notes, Fall, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Univesity Archivist, Acting, November, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - St. Joseph's, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Founder's Day, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - G57.1010 Fall, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Survey, Syllabi, Etc, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Intro. Course, undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Introductory Course Exercises, undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - G57.2010 Arch Hist Soc & Hist Ed Princ & Practicum (II), Spring, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - 2010 Syllabus-orig, undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Research/Reading Courses, 1985-1990 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Archives Program Budget, Period Ended August 1979, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Program Review, undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - G57.1010 Fall, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Conservation and Micrographics, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Community & Local, undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - G57.2017 Burke Spring 1987 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Adjunct Courses, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Orig. Form, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - G57.1010 Fall, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - G57.1010 Fall, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Topics in Archives & Editing: 2019, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227171 1
  - Manuscript & Conservation, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Archives, HIstorical Societies and Historical Editing Practicums I & II, G57.1010, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Computers & Archival Administration, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Seminar in Historical Editing, G57.1012, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Local and Community History, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Adm. History & Records Management, G57.2016, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Micrographics, G57.2013, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Historian and the Visual Record, G57.2019, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Media & History, G57.1775, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Abraham, Balzarini & Frantilla: "What is Backlog is Prologue", undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Albritton, Jane: "Preserving Art for the People", undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - The American Image: "Intro: Photos As Symbolic History", undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Anderson, Dr. Joseph: "Public Welfare Case Records: A Study of Archival Practices", undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Angel, Herbert: "Archival Janus: The Records Center", undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Baragwanath, Albert: "Dating Photographs", undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Barrow, W. J.: "The Barrow Method of Restoring Deteriorated Documents", undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Barrow, W. J.: "Migration of Impurities in Paper", undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Becker, Ronald L.: "On Deposit: A Handshake and A Lawsuit", undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Bibliography of Fundraising Publications, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Blendon, Edith James: "University Archives: A Reason for Existence", 1975 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Bloch, Milton J.: "A Case of Boredom", undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Bolotenko, George: "Instant Professionalism: To The Shiny New Men of the Future", undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Brown, Richard Maxwell: "The Archives of Violence", undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Buchen, Philip: "Secrets of History & The Law of Secrets", 1977 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Burckel, Nicholas: "The Expanding Role", undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Caplow, Theodore: "Dynamics of Info. Interviewing", undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Cappon, Lester J.: "Historical Manuscripts as Archives", undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Cappon, Lester: "What, Then, Is There To Theorize About?", undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Cloud, Patricia: "The Cost of Converting To MARC AMC", undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Cohen, D. & Miller, F.: "Urban Archives: An Annotated Bibliography", undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Cohen, Patricia: "Statistics and the State" (G57.1010), undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Conservation of Library & Archival Materials-NY State, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Cozort Day, Deborah: "Appraisal Guidelines For Reprint Collections", undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Crawford, Miriam: "Interpreting the University Archives to the Librarian", undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Cross Norton, Margaret: "The Classification & Description of Archives", undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Danielson, Elena S.: "The Ethics of Success", undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Danovitch, Sylvia: "The Past Recaptured? Photo Record of the Internment of Japanese-Americans", undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Doy, Gen: "The Camera Against the Paris Commune", undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Ehrenberg, Ralph: "Aural and Graphic Archives & Manuscripts", not dated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Elston, Charles: "University Student Records: Research Use, Privacy Rights & the Buckley Law", undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Espinosa, Robert: "The Book & Paper Group Annual", undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Evans, Frank: Reading Lists-"Intro. To Modern Archives", undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Gabehart, Alan: "Qualifications Desired by Employers for Entry-Level Archivists in the U.S.", undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Gilliland, Anne: "The Development of Automated Archival Systems", undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Glassie, Henry: "Folklorist Thought on the Problems of Oral History", undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Gondos, Victor Jr.: "American Archival Architecture", undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Goodwyn, Lawrence: "Populist Dreams & Negro Rights", undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Grele, Ronald: "On Using Oral History Collections: An Intro.", undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Grele, Ronald: "A Surmisable Variety: Interdisciplinarity and Oral Testimony", undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Griffith, R. & Theoharis, A.: "Original Essays on the Cold War & the Origins of McCarthyism", undated (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Haas, Pamela: "The Conservation of Photograph Collections", undated (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Ham, Gerald: "Archival Choices…", undated (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Hart, Ellis & Pritchard: "Appraisal & Scheduling of Government Records", undated (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Hersh, Seymour: "Nixon's Last Cover-Up", undated (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Higham, J. & Zangrando, R.: "Statement on Plagiarism", undated (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - History of NYU, Chapter XI, "The School of Law", undated (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - History of NYU, Chapter XVI, "The Washington Square College", undated (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Holloran, Peter: "Rediscovering Lost Values", undated (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Hook, Sidney: "Academic Freedom & Communism", undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Hunter, Gregory: "Thinking Small to Think Big…", undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Huskamp Peterson, Trudy: "Archives Principles & Records of the New Technology", undated (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - "Insouciant & Independent: New Beginnings at Washington Square", undated (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - James Blendon, Edith: "Univ. Archives: Reason for Existence", undated (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Jarmul, David: "Some Old Ideas Still Work for Preserving Historic Records", undated (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Journal of American History: "Exhibition Reviews" (Several Authors), undated (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Journal of the Institute of Paper Conservation: "The Paper Conservator," Volume 3, 1978, undated (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Kahn, Herman: "Some Comments on the Archival Vocation", undated (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Karamanski, Theodore J.: "Roundtable: Ethics and Public History", undated (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Kepley, David: "Sampling in Archives: A Review", undated (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Kesner, Richard M.: "Archival Collection Development", undated (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Kline, Mary Jo: "A Guide to Documentary Editing", undated (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Kohn, Richard: "The Future of the Historical Profession", undated (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Larson, Arthur: "Administrative History: A Proposal For A Re- Evaluation of its Contributions to the Archival Profession", undated (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Leaper, Rae: "What's in the Box", undated (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Leland, Waldo G.: "Prehistory & Origins of the NHPRC", undated (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Lemisch, Jesse: "The Papers of a Few Great Black Men and a Few Great White Women", undated (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Leo Baeck Institute: "Library & Archives News", undated (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Link, Arthur, ed.: "The Papers of Woodrow Wilson", undated (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Lockwood, Elizabeth: "Imponderable Matters…", 1990 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - MacGregor Burns, James: Keynote Address, undated (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Maedke, Robek & Brown: "Information & Records Management", undated (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Malan, Nancy: "Organizing Photo Collections…", undated (Box 12, Folder 83)
  - Malmgreen, Gail: "Labor & the Holocaust", undated (Box 12, Folder 84)
  - McCree, Mary Lynn: "Good Sense & Good Judgement", undated (Box 12, Folder 85)
  - McLaughlin Green, Constance: "The Value of Local History", undated (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Meiklejohn, Alexander: "Should Communists Be Allowed to Teach?", undated (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Miller, Page Putnam & Thelen, David: "Reconnecting Historians & Archivists", undated (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Moseley, Eva: "Sources for the 'New Women's History'", undated (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - NYU Archives: Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - NYU Archives: Collection Development Statement, undated (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Penn, Ira: "Federal Records Management in the '80s", undated (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Pettit, Marilyn: "Processing An Archival Collection: Instructions & Guidelines for NYU Archives", undated (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Posner, Ernest: "Some Aspects of Archival Development Since the French Revolution", undated (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Potts, David: "College Archives As Windows on American Society", undated (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Rhoads, James: "One Man's Hopes For His Society, His Profession, His Country", undated (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Roberts, John: "Archival Theory: Much Ado About Shelving", undated (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Robertson, Peter: "More Than Meets The Eye", undated (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Rofes, William (ed.): "A Basic Glossary for Archivists, Manuscript Curators & Records Managers", undated (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Romney, Joseph: "Legal Considerations in Oral History", undated (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Rumer, Thomas: "Corporate History & The Records Manager", undated (Box 12, Folder 101)
  - Rundell, Walter Jr.: Local Sources, From: In Pursuit of American History, undated (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - Rundell, Walter Jr.: "Photographs as Historical Evidence: Early Texas Oil", undated (Box 12, Folder 103)
  - Photo Readings (binder), undated (Box 12, Folder 104)
  - SAA, 1989-1993 (Box 12, Folder 105)
  - SAA Education Directory, 1986-1991 (Box 12, Folder 106)
  - Saffady, William: "A University & Records Management Program: Some Operational Guidelines", undated (Box 12, Folder 107)
  - Sanders, Robert L.: "Company Index: Info. Retrieval Thesauri for Organizations & Institutions", undated (Box 12, Folder 108)
  - Schwarz, Judith: "The Archivist Balancing Act: Helping Researchers While Protecting Privacy", undated (Box 12, Folder 109)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Jr.: "What is Loyalty: A Difficult Question", undated (Box 12, Folder 110)
  - Schmidt & Wilson: "A Practical Approach to University Records Management", undated (Box 12, Folder 111)
  - Schulz, Constance B.: "From Generation Unto Generation", undated (Box 12, Folder 112)
  - Simmons, Ruth: "Legal, Ethical Issues Packet", undated (Box 12, Folder 113)
  - Smith & Steadman: "Present Value of Corporate History", undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
  - SAA, Automating the Archives, A Beginners Guide, undated (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Society of American Archivists: "A Code of Ethics For Archivists", undated (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Society of American Archivists: "Joint Statement on Access to Original Research Materials in Libraries", undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Moseley, Eva: "Visiting Archives in China", undated (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Moss, William: "Oral History", undated (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Moss, William: "Oral History: An Appreciation", undated (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Mucci, Paul: "Paper & Leather Conservation: A Manual", undated (Box 12, Folder 121)
  - Neuenschwander, John: "Remembrance of Things Past", undated (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - Nevins, Allan: "Oral History: How & Why It Was Born", undated (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Norris, Thomas D.: "Processing Extremely Large Collections of Historical Photos", undated (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227172 9
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - StudentFiles, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227173 7
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 55)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04227174 7
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Student Files, A-S, 1977-1993, undated (Box 13, Folder 64)